{
    "id": "684e1bce588f42fa95f1a24ac204226e",
    "title": "Beginner Level Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Both my parents …………………………… me.",
            "description": "Use a plural verb after both.",
            "answers": [
                "adore",
                "adores"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7301ea64ea134ff387bd66cbe04e6c21"
        },
        {
            "question": "Each of my sisters …………………………… me.",
            "description": "Use a singular verb after each.",
            "answers": [
                "love",
                "loves"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ca18e4c8a2f7426796f768900d93e545"
        },
        {
            "question": "They all helped …………………………….",
            "description": "Use each other to talk about two people or thing use one another for more than two. ",
            "answers": [
                "each other",
                "one another"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f0e8901105d6407e915451223bfe409a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The two brothers quarreled with ………………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "each other",
                "one another"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "46f2186ff4b848e4848ba2d7bc86785a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not as tall as …………………………….. is",
            "description": "The subject form of the pronoun is used before a verb.",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "14f2a55e9ab542df84d79877c64a60ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your need is greater than ………………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "my",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1dafe640fd0f40bca40be23166cf0a2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "That child of …………………………….. has broken my window again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0422c0a8df784990ac6429cddf863a86"
        },
        {
            "question": "Both Sam and Manual ……………………………. to be blamed for this.",
            "description": "Use a plural verb after both. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "edf5a12bfbee4da8801a781c42435650"
        },
        {
            "question": "He and …………………………… are partners.",
            "description": "When the pronoun is the subject, its subject form is used. ",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "48a4246c947847dc9a99018a55228802"
        },
        {
            "question": "None of us …………………………….. heard anything from him since then.",
            "description": "A singular verb is preferred after none. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0e78b748b6394d6cae5fecead2c25073"
        },
        {
            "question": "My house is bigger than ……………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "my friend",
                "that of my friend"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c5afc2e29c0e482c9dfc173b76f6b13f"
        },
        {
            "question": "It …………………………….. a stormy day, we didn’t go out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "being",
                "was",
                "been",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "777ed398714746aca8edec5eee45d787"
        }
    ]
}